NITZAN COHEN

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

Rishon LeZiyyon +972-50-3131570 (074-7271127) nitzancohen@hotmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/nitzancohen-web https://github.com/NitzanCO7

PROFILE SUMMARY

As a web developer with over 10 years of experience in the education field, I have a unique perspective on the power of technology in enhancing the learning process. Specializing in implementing cutting-edge technological tools, I have been able to make a positive impact on the lives of students with diverse learning needs.

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

JS TS HTML CSS React Redux Next.js Node.js Express.js MongoDB Redis Git Python Vercel

WORK EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Developer | SRISA (Santa Reparata Internetional School of Arts)

2023 - present

• Full Stack developer focusing on the client side in the SRISA project, utilizing Next.js, TypeScript, MongoDB, and ManteinUI. Collaborating with a team to implement key features in an application that facilitates students in searching for and borrowing books for their academic needs.

Front-End Developer DEAN Intelligence

2023 - present

• Frontend developer with expertise in Next.js, TypeScript, and proficiency in Hebrew, responsible for creating and adjusting websites to meet the requirements of Hebrew-speaking Israeli users.

Web Developer Freelancer

2022 - present

• Developed and powered a dynamic, responsive, and user-friendly single-page application (SPA) for a small businesses using React.js (shayelbornshtein.com, Running Trainer, we-talk.fun)

Special Education Teacher | Ministry of Education

2016 - present

- Implemented the use of advanced technology across my team, such as assistive devices and adaptive software, to enhance learning experiences and promote student independence.
- Specialized in providing individualized instruction and support to students with diverse learning needs and disabilities.
- Implemented evidence-based teaching strategies and accommodations to meet the unique needs of each student and improve their academic and social outcomes.
- Collaborated with interdisciplinary teams, including speech therapists, occupational. therapists, and parents, to develop and implement individualized education plans (IEPs)

Long-Distances Running Coach Eitan - Everybody can

2019 - present

Training people with autism in athletics fields to improve their motor skills and also their communication skills.

Mentor National Service

2007 - 2010

Volunteer at Association for children with Cerebral Palsy (CP) in Rishon LeZiyyon.

EDUCATION

Full Stack Web DevelopmentTripleTen by Yandex & MasterSchool2021 - 2022

Long-Distances Running Coach Certificate School of Sport Professions 2019

Teacher Certificate in Special Education Ohalo Academic College 2016 - 2017

BA Special Education Tel-Hai Academic College 2011 - 2016

Practical Electronics Engineering Mekif Gimel "Amit Amal" 2005 - 2007

LANGUAGES

Hebrew Native English Full working proficiency